<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="help_home">
        "The home view is the primary interaction point of the application. You can subscribe to any desired topic by pressing the Plus button on the bottom right of your screen. You will be prompted to enter the topic you wish to subscribe to, then you must select an interaction type for the card. Selecting an inappropriate interaction type to some topics may yield unexpected results, but in most cases it should not be a problem."
    </string>
    <string name="help_settings">
        "The Settings view is for setting the user's profile name and the server\'s address. Not setting these correctly will show an error that explains the exact problem that occurred. You cannot start a connection with a blank username or no connection address."
    </string>
    <string name="help_connect">
        "To connect to the MQTT Broker, navigate to the "Settings" view and enter your desired username and the address of the broker. You don\'t have to provide a port number since it\'s preconfigured serverside. If the connection fails, please double-check the address or contact the system administrator. Upon a successful connection you can navigate to the home view and start using the app."
    </string>
    <string name="help_deleteUser">
        "To delete a user profile, tap the "Delete Profile" button, and select the desired profile from the drop-down menu and press delete. This will permanently delete the selected user's stored data such as subscribed topics, cards and other saved values."
    </string>
    <string name="help_subscribe">
        "To subscribe to a topic you must tap the plus button on the home view, in the bottom right corner of your screen, after which you will be prompted to enter the topic you wish to subscribe to. After that you must select an interaction type from several options in a drop-down menu. Selecting an appropriate interaction type to the topic is important, as you cannot control a thermostat with a single button, or cannot turn on/off a lamp with a text input."
    </string>
    <string name="help_unsubscribe">
        "To unsubscribe from a topic, simply long-press any of the existing cards, then select "Unsubscribe" from the context menu and the card will be deleted from the Home view."
    </string>
    <string name="help_card">
        "Each card is split into 2 halves. On it's left half the card's subscribed topic is visible, on the right half the selected interaction type. Every card will send a message to the server based on it's interaction type to the given topic. This message will reach every smart device that uses this topic."
    </string>
</resources>